Poco! Who do you think you are, being out at such a late hour?!
♬(ｵｰﾌﾟﾆﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
D-Dad...
I'm glad that you're safe, but...
W-Where's my sister?
She got worried and went off looking for you!
♬ 空 こぼれ落ちたふたつの星が
She... She went outside?!
♬ 光と闇の水面
吸い込まれてゆく
Poco, what's gotten into you?
This isn't like you.
Sis...
♬ 引き合うように 重なる波紋
Sis!
♬～
♬ 誇りの道を往く者に
太陽の導きを
♬ 野望の果てを目指す者に
生け贄を
Sora koboreochita futatsu no hoshi ga
Two stars fall from the sky
Original Translation:
Mudasubs
Hikari to yami no minamo suikomareteyuku
One shining in the light, the other sinking into darkness
♬～
Hikiau you ni kasanaru hamon
A ripple drawing the two of them together
♬ 震えるほど心
燃え尽きるほど熱く
♬ その手から放て 鼓動
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Distro:
ExWizzard
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Distro:
ExWizzard
♬ 身体 漲る勇気で
Hokori no michi wo yuku mono ni taiyou no michibiki wo
One will walk the path of pride and receive the sun's guidance
♬ 迷いなき覚悟に喝采を
Yabou no hate wo mezasu mono ni
One will walk the path of unbridled ambition...
♬ その血の運命 ジョジョ
Ikenie wo
Demanding sacrifice!
♬～
Furueru hodo kokoro moetsukiru hodo atsuku
Let that burning in your soul calm the trembling of your heart
Timing/Typesetting/Encoding:
Fadeout4
Sono te kara hanate kodou
Strike down your fears,
Karada minagiru yuuki de
With courage coursing through your veins!
Mayou naki kakugo ni kassai wo
You cannot overcome your pain unless you can accept...
Raw Hunter:
WRRRRY
Sono chi no sadame
The legacy of your bloodline!
Jojo!
http://www.some-stuffs.com/
Episode 8: "Jojo & Dio's Bloody Battle!"
(人面犬)ウシャシャシャ！
(ﾃﾞｨｵ)例えば… だ｡
Allow me to give you a metaphor.
例えば この 美しい花だ｡
Much like this exquisite rose,
your beauty has only just begun to bloom.
君は 花でいえば ちょうど➡
このぐらいの若さといえる｡
But consider this, Mademoiselle.
よ～く 考えてみたまえ
マドモアゼル｡
Once a flower has bloomed,
all that remains for it is to wither away and die.
この花は
このまま 咲き盛ってしまえば➡
後は 枯れゆくのみ｡
悲しいとは 思わないかい？
Such a pity, isn't it?
The little lady is sixteen years old!
彼女は 16歳｡ 正真正銘の生娘！
Truly a prime virgin!
She's absolutely radiating delicious life energy!
生命エネルギーが みなぎってて
おいしそう｡
Right, Master Dio?
でしょ？ ディオ様｡
ウシャシャシャ！
ちっ！
ヒャヒャヒャ！
(人面犬)ぐあっ！
Those without a sense of etiquette have no right to live.
礼儀を知らん者は
生きる価値なしだな｡
Now then, Mademoiselle. I have a proposition for you.
どうだね？ マドモアゼル｡
１つ 選択してくれるかね？
Wouldn't it be lovely to spend eternity in the prime of your youth?
今のままの 若さで➡
永遠を 楽しみたいとは
思わないかい？
You see I, the mighty Dio, am not the type to
force someone into companionship, unlike other men...
とはいってもだ｡ この ディオ➡
友情を押しつける類いの
やからとは 違うのでね｡
You will choose your fate, and it will be of your own free will.
君の自由意思｡
君の運命は 自分で選ぶんだ｡
(ポコの姉)化け物…｡
え？ 聞こえないよ｡
Monster...
Eh? I didn't quite get that.
You're doomed to be cursed for all eternity... you m-monster!
あなたは 永遠に呪われている➡
ば… 化け物よ！
(ﾄﾞｩｰﾋﾞｰ)ウシュ…｡
(ﾄﾞｩｰﾋﾞｰ)ウシュー｡
Eh... It's quite the pity, having to part ways so soon after we met.
え～ 出会ったばかりで
もう お別れとは 遺憾に思うが…｡
But before you go...
紹介するよ｡
彼の名は 怪人ドゥービー｡
This is Doobie, the Monstrous.
この ディオが
お気に召さんのなら➡
And if the company of the great Dio is not to your liking,
then perhaps he will better entertain you.
彼に相手してもらうといい｡
Bye, Mademoiselle!
バーイ マドモアゼル！
(ﾄﾞｩｰﾋﾞｰ)グモー｡
(ポコの姉)ああっ！
(ﾄﾞｩｰﾋﾞｰ)グモッ！
(ポコの姉)キャー！
キャーッ！
ああ～！
(ﾄﾞｩｰﾋﾞｰ)はぁ… はぁ…｡
(ﾄﾞｩｰﾋﾞｰ)アンギャアアーッ！
だ… 誰だ～!?
Who did that?!
(ｼﾞｮﾅｻﾝ)さあ 誰かな？
Who indeed.
ゾンビになど 誇りある
我が名を教える 必要なし！
I don't see why I should share my name with such a lowly zombie!
Sis!
姉ちゃん！
(ポコの姉)ポコ！
Poco!
(ﾄﾞｩｰﾋﾞｰ)HOOORRRRRRYYYN！
ぬおおおおお！
あっ…｡
(ﾄﾞｩｰﾋﾞｰ)WOOOOKYAAAAAHH！
かんじゃった！ かんじゃった！➡
You really fell for it!
いっぱい かんでやったぜ！
何かいる！ あの頭の中｡
What is that, moving inside his head?
W-What...
い… 一体!?
ああっ！
(ﾄﾞｩｰﾋﾞｰ)ルン ルン ルン！
フフフ…｡
That zombie... has snakes slithering inside of him!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)あ… あのゾンビ！
体内に 蛇を飼ってるんだ！
それも 猛毒のコブラとか
肉を食いちぎる 奇妙な蛇を！
And not just any snakes, venomous cobras and ones that eat human flesh!
You've been bitten!
(ﾄﾞｩｰﾋﾞｰ)たまげたか？
Those poisonous snakes bit him... m-more than once!
(ポコ)
兄ちゃんが 毒蛇にかまれた！➡
そ… それも いっぱい！
USHYAAA！
What a nuisance.
やれやれだ｡
ディオの悪趣味に
つきあっている時間はない！
I don't have time to waste on Dio's twisted underlings!
(ﾄﾞｩｰﾋﾞｰ)ウシャー！
おりゃ！
ふん！
He's strong...
(ﾀﾞｲｱｰ)ほう 強い｡
毒まで搾り出したぞ｡
He even managed to squeeze out the venom.
It's amazing he gained such control over
the flow of his blood in such a short time.
短期間で よくぞ ここまで➡
血液の流れを コントロールできる
ようになったものだ｡
ツェペリさんが 生命エネルギーを
ジョースターさんに与えて➡
It's because old man Zeppeli passed his
life force on to Mr. Joestar before he died!
死んでいったからだ｡
ほんの少しだけ 波紋を送り込んで
蛇の血液を とち狂わしてやる！
It only takes a bit of Ripple energy to manipulate these snakes!
うわぁぁぁ！
(ポコ)姉ちゃん！
(ポコの姉)ポコ!?
Sis!
Poco!
(ポコ)姉ちゃん！
♬～
ふん！
あっ！
I've returned from hell, Dio!
地獄から戻ってきたぞ ディオ！
So, you're still alive, Jojo...
生きてたのか ジョジョ…｡
I suppose that means you managed to defeat those knights, correct?
ということは あの２人の騎士を
倒してきたということらしいな｡
Master Dio! Give us the order and we'll execute him!
(ﾍﾟｲｼﾞ)ディオ様！
ここは 俺たちに やつの処刑を➡
命令してくだせえ｡
(ｼﾞｮｰﾝｽﾞ)
この牙の歯形としてくれましょう｡
Let us bury him in our fangs!
ディオ！
いや… こいつだけは➡
Dio!
No! This one, here...
Leave this one to me, the mighty Dio!
こいつだけは
この ディオがやる！
I'll be honest, Jojo.
正直 言うとだ ジョジョ｡
I did not want to have to be the one to kill you...
俺はな お前を
この手に かけたくなかったのだ｡
I find little amusement at the thought of turning
the man I was raised with, my own brother, into an undead.
幼なじみで
共に 同じ家で育った お前を➡
アンデッドにしても
面白くも何ともないんでな｡
That's why I intended for those two knights to handle it.
だから あの ２騎士に
処刑を任せてしまったのだ｡
However, I see now it was naive not to finish you off myself.
だがな…
最後の詰めで 俺は甘かった…｡
生きている 貴様を見て
それは 帝王としての➡
Seeing you alive has shown me the error of my ways;
the one fatal flaw of the mighty Dio.
この ディオの精神的弱さと
悟ったよ｡
But now, I see it is up to me to tear you limb from limb!
今！ ためらいもなく
貴様を惨殺処刑してくれよう！
同じこと！
お前を葬るのに 罪悪感なし！
The feeling is mutual! I feel no guilt in putting an end to you!
By the way, Jojo...
それはそうと ジョジョ➡
あの 派手な帽子の
ひげの おっさんは どうしたね？
Where is that old man with the ridiculous hat and mustache?
どこに いるんだ？
Where could he have gone?
ディオ！
僕の気持ちを 聞かせてやる｡
Dio... let me tell you how I feel.
Although it is unbecoming of a gentleman...
紳士として 恥ずべきことだが➡
To be perfectly honest, right now I, Jonathan Joestar...
正直なところ 今の
ジョナサン･ジョースターは➡
...would like nothing more than to avenge
the people you've killed, Dio! Prepare to die!
恨みを晴らすために ディオ！
貴様を殺すのだ！
ふん！ 来い ジョジョ！
Come, Jojo!
来い ジョジョ！
おおおおおお～！
ダ… ダイアーさん!?
ジョジョ お前は下がっていろ｡
Mr. Dire!
Get back, Jojo!
I, Dire, have greater claim for vengeance against this fiend!
やつへの 恨みなら➡
この ダイアーが
先に 晴らす権利がある｡➡
Zeppeli and I shared a 20 year friendship,
forged in the rigor of our harsh training!
ツェペリさんとは
共に 苦行を乗り越えた➡
20年来の親友だったのだ！
ディオとかいうやつ！
この ダイアーが➡
Dio, listen!
Let it be known that I, Dire, shall send you into the fiery depths of hell!
地獄のふちに 沈めてやる！
やめろ！ ディオには➡
Stop! Dio has hidden powers that you've never dealt with!
あなたの知らない
隠された能力がある！
あっ！
ん？ ほう…｡
That is quite the interesting footwork...
面白い動きだ｡
人間というものは➡
I suppose you humans can achieve that level of agility through mere effort.
修行しだいで こういう 不思議な
身の軽やかさも 体得できるのか｡
ふん！
だがな この ディオは➡
But in just one night, the mighty Dio has
surpassed even the most extraordinary of mortals!
一夜にして この世の
どんな超人をも 超えたのよ｡
Wrrryyyyyyy!
UREYYYYY！
そんな 眠っちまいそうな
のろい動きで➡
You think that pathetic looking kick
will be enough to defeat me, the mighty Dio?!
この ディオが倒せるか!?
WOOOORYYYYYAAA！
ふん！
ぬぅ！
かかったな アホが！➡
You fell for it, fool!
Thunder Cross Split Attack!
サンダークロス
スプリットアタック！
Amazing!
すげえ！ クロスさせることで
攻撃と同時に➡
This technique is allowing him to attack and
keep his opponent from defending with their arms!
相手に さらすことになる
ボディーを防御する！
It's a perfect offense and defense!
攻守において 完璧だ！
No martial artist has ever successfully defended against it!
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)これを破った格闘者は
１人としていない！
うっ！
ああっ！
That's-
あれは!?
Useless, useless, useless, useless!
無駄 無駄 無駄 無駄！
う… 動かん！
I... can't move!
His dehydration freeze!
気化冷凍法！
He withdraws all fluid from his body in an instant,
dropping his temperature to steal body heat from his enemy!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)相手の体内の水分を
一瞬にして 気化させることから➡
熱を奪い 凍らせる！➡
When Dio freezes the body, he halts the flow of blood,
effectively stopping the Ripple along with it!
体を凍らせれば
血液の流れから作る 波紋は➡
ディオには
決して 流れることはない！➡
B-But even I'm shocked at Dio displaying such power!
それにしても
すさまじいのは ディオの能力！➡
Now he can freeze an entire body in an instant!
体全体を 一瞬のうちとは！
き… 貴様…｡
Y-You bastard!
Weakling, weakling!
貧弱 貧弱！
ちょいとでも 俺にかなうとでも
思ったか？ まぬけが！
Did you really think you could stand up to me, you utter fool?!
Coming here has guaranteed that you will die like a dog!
貴様らは 犬死にするために
ここへ 来たのだ！
Now, allow me to provide you with the most vicious death I can offer!
よって 最も残酷な 死を贈ろう！
D-Dire!
ダ… ダイアー！
やめろ～！
Stop!
(ﾀﾞｲｱｰ)うわあああ～！
うっ… うう…｡
ジョジョ！ いくぞ｡
Jojo! Let's begin.
You'll be the next I send into oblivion!
次に 死の忘却を
迎え入れるのは お前よ！
(ﾀﾞｲｱｰ)うう…｡
あっ！
ダイアー！
Dire!
フフ… 波紋入りの
バラのとげは 痛かろう…｡
Thorns from a rose infused with a Ripple are quite poisonous, aren't they?
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)ダイアー！
ダイアーさん！
Dire!
Mr. Dire!
ぬぅ… よ… よくも！
How... How dare you...
How dare you scratch my face!
よくも 俺の顔に傷をつけたな！
ダイアーさん｡ くっ…｡
Mr. Dire...
Speedwagon!
スピードワゴン！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)おう！
Yeah!
Dio, the key to defeating your dehydration freeze...
ディオ！
お前の気化冷凍法！
いかにして破るか！
どうやって 波紋を送り込むか！
The key to finally piercing you with a Ripple...
Mr. Dire has just shown me the key to defeating you!
その突破口 今
ダイアーさんが 教えてくれたぞ！
I'll charge it with the Ripple, and then strike you down with
the hero Bruford's sword imbued with Luck and Pluck!
波紋を込めて
この 勇者ブラフォードの➡
幸運と勇気の剣で斬る！
Good Fortune
Courage
うう…｡
You're all lower than frog piss...
カエルの小便よりも げすな…｡
You and that damned Ripple!
げすな波紋なぞを よくも…｡
You dare strike me with it?!
よくも この俺に！
Know your god-damned place!
いい気になるなよ！ KUAA！
I'm going to feed you all to the undead!
てめえら全員
アンデッドどもの餌だ！
I'll make sure each of you pissants is turned into mincemeat!
青ちょびた面を
餌としてやるぜ！
出たな！ やつの この世の
どんな悪よりも どす黒い性格が！
There it is! That's the twisted personality I sensed,
more gruesome than any villain I've ever met!
He was simply hiding behind a mask of calm and gallantry!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)これまでの 冷静さや
ダンディーな態度など➡
単なる 仮面にすぎねえ！➡
This is his true nature!
これが やつの本性！➡
Now he's finally been outed, just from the shame
of having tasted the Ripple for the first time!
初めて味わった やつの
屈辱的 波紋初体験ってわけよ！
この ストレイツォ 容赦せん！
I, Straits, will show no mercy!
The name's Page!
俺の名は ペイジ｡
ジョーンズ｡
Jones!
Plant!
プラント｡
ボーンナム｡
Bonham!
(一同)血管針攻撃！
Blood Vessel Skewering!
ぐあっ！
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)バラは 生き物だから➡
Since a rose is a living thing, it can carry
the power of the Ripple when it's released from one's hand...
その 樹液中に
波紋を帯びさせたまま➡
放つことができるが
金属は 生物ではないので…｡
But seeing as metal is not alive...
(一同)アギャアッ！
(ｽﾄﾚｲﾂｫ)
触れて流さねばならない！
...I must channel it directly.
(ｿﾞﾝﾋﾞたち)グヘヘヘ…｡
(ﾄﾝﾍﾟﾃｨ)
うじゃうじゃと 湧きおるわ｡➡
They keep coming...
Lad, let us take care of these underlings.
どれ 雑魚は引き受けよう｡
ふん！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)この スピードワゴンが
判断する限り➡
From what I can see, Dio could match the speed of a cheetah!
ディオの動きのスピードは
動物のヒョウぐらいか｡➡
ツェペリさんの波紋法を
身につけた 今なら➡
With the power of Zeppeli's Ripple added
to his own, he should be able to keep up!
見切ることは可能！
こおおおおお！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
しかし やつのパワーは➡
However, Dio is so strong, he can destroy
flesh and bone with the lightest touch!
骨肉を たやすく
みじんに砕くほど 無双だ！
It would end in an instant...
勝負は一瞬！
The battle will be decided as soon as they make contact!
２人のすれ違いざま
決着がつくはず！
WRRRYYYY！
うぉぉぉぉ！
I'll drain the life right out of you!
搾り取ってやる！ 貴様の命を！
清めてやる！ その汚れたる野望！
I'll purify your twisted ambition!
W-When did he grab those roses?!
こ… こいつは
いつの間に バラを隠し持った!?
Wrryyyyy!
WRRRRRRY！
Now's my chance!
今だ！
う… うまい！
G-Good! He circled around to Dio's right!
ディオの右へ 回り込んだ！
右目は 死角になっている！
He's blind on that side!
おおおお！
し… しまった！
D-Damn it! His fighting skills have improved!
こいつ！ 戦い慣れてやがる！
ふん！
GYYYYAAAAAA！
おおっ！
や… やった！
H-He's got him!
うぉぉぉぉ～！
He finally defeated Dio!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
ついに倒したぞ！ ディオを！
ガボ ガ… ガボ…｡
違うね まぬけどもが！
Not quite!
You damned buffoon!
なっ!?
こ… これは！
It... can't be...
It's frozen!
凍っている！
Weakling, weakling!
貧弱 貧弱！
Wrrrryyyy!
WRRRRYYYY！
Now you will become another one of my children of the night!
これで 貴様も
我が夜の しもべとなるんだ！
うう… うっ！
KWAHHH！
こりこり弾力ある けい動脈に
触っているぞ ジョジョ！
I'm caressing your carotid artery as we speak, Jojo!
This warm, throbbing pulse...
この 温かい弾力｡
心地いい感触よ！
...It's quite the sensation.
K-Kick!
け… 蹴りだ！
ふん！
うう… 足にまで冷凍法を！
My legs are frozen, too!
Useless, useless, useless, useless!
無駄 無駄 無駄 無駄！
Try to hold still, Jojo!
しょげかえってろ ジョジョ！
Otherwise this delicate little vessel might be severed.
動くと この デリケートな管が
プチンと 切れるじゃあないか｡
これから つまんでいる こいつに
ちょいと 傷をつけ➡
And I'll have none of that, not when I plan to knick it
just enough to exchange my vampiric fluids for your blood!
貴様の生命と
俺の 吸血鬼のエキスとを➡
循環交換してやるのだからなあ！
I-I have to help him!
た… 助けなくては！
ゾンビども！
My zombies!
Keep those pissants out of my hair for just a moment!
少しの時間 そこの
青ちょびた連中を よこすなよ！
次から次へと 切りがないわい｡
They aren't relenting!
これでは 助けに行けない｡
We don't stand a chance of saving him!
Now then, Jojo.
さあ ジョジョ｡
It's finally time to receive my fluids and become my servant!
俺の しもべとなるため
吸血鬼のエキスを 拝領するのだ！
Dio, it isn't over yet!
ディオ 勝ったと思うな！
お前は 今
ミスを犯しているんだ！
There's just one fatal flaw in your plan!
何だと!?
And what's that?!
フッ それは
僕の生命を吸い取るために➡
You left the rest of my body unfrozen so you could drain my blood!
僕の全身を
凍らせていないことだ！
全身を 凍らせれば
波紋は 流れないが➡
Freezing my body prevents the Ripple from flowing.
However, it also prevents you from draining my life energy!
しかし！ お前も
生命エネルギーを 吸い取れない！
This is your one fatal flaw!
それが お前が犯している
戦法上のミスだ！
ん？
こいつ 炎であぶってやがった！
He's using the torch to thaw out!
This can't be... The heat from that flame is
more intense than the cold from dehydrating him!
まずい！ 気化熱で 冷凍するより
火炎の熱伝導の方が 強いのか!?
He'll use the sword to channel the Ripple...
剣を伝わって 波紋が！
ふん！
サンライトイエロー
オーバードライブ‼
Sunlight Yellow...
Overdrive!
食らえ！
Take this!
He got him!
入った！
いや！ よく見ろ！
No, look again!
It seems as if the Ripple has failed!
あの 手応えでは
波紋は失敗じゃな｡
え!?
My arm... My arm is frozen again!
腕が！
腕が また 凍らされている！
He can freeze me just from touch!
顔に触れただけで 凍るのか！
Not good enough, Jojo!
詰めが甘かったな ジョジョ！
なっ！
この ディオ➡
I, Dio, must admit that your ingenuity in
times of desperation is quite impressive.
貴様の精神の爆発力 認めよう｡
And your plan with the fire was equally impressive.
今の 炎であぶる 思いつき➡
素晴らしいものが
あったことも認めよう｡
んん～｡
But come now, Jojo. You have no way of
defeating my freezing technique.
だが ジョジョ！
この ディオの冷凍法は
絶対 破れん！
腕１本なら 触れただけで十分！
You've seen what I did to your arm.
I can freeze your entire body solid in a mere two seconds!
全身でも
２秒で 完璧に仕上げようぞ｡
ぐぐっ…｡
はぁ…｡
吸血鬼のエキスを
搾り出したのか｡
He expelled the vampiric fluid... Mr. Joestar hasn't given up just yet!
ジョースターさんは
まだ 諦めていねえ！
何だ!? その 緊張した構えは｡
まだ やる気か!?
Whatever is that tense looking stance for?
Do you still intend to fight?
あがいても あがいても
人間の努力には 限界があるのさ！
Struggle all you like, but remember
you're limited to what you can do as a mortal.
波紋法の修行努力など➡
All your training to master this Ripple technique has been...
無駄 無駄 無駄 無駄 無駄 無駄
無駄 無駄 無駄 無駄 無駄 無駄！
Useless, useless, useless, useless, useless, useless,
useless, useless, useless, useless, useless, useless!
A monkey cannot surpass a human!
モンキーが 人間に追いつけるか！
お前は この ディオにとっての
モンキーなんだよ ジョジョ！
Because when faced with the mighty Dio,
you are nothing more than a mere monkey, Jojo!
You're wrong!
違う！ 信念さえあれば
人間に不可能はない！
If a man has faith, he can accomplish anything!
人間は成長するのだ！
してみせる！
Humanity can evolve, and so can I!
I'm afraid that you can't!
できないね！
貴様は ゾンビになるからな！
Especially not once you've become my zombie!
Wrryyyyyyy!!
WOOOORRRYYYYYY！
うお～！
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)
手が！ 手が燃えている！
His hand! It's on fire!
He lit his glove on fire!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)手袋に 火をつけた！
That might be enough to overpower the freezing technique!
あれなら
冷凍法を 破れるかもしれない！
You're about to learn which one of us will taste defeat in the end, Dio!
最後の最後に
敗北するのは どちらか➡
今 分かるぞ ディオ！
うっしゃあああ‼
WRRRRRYYY!
WRRRRYYY！
と… 止められたか!?
H-He blocked it!
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)いや！ 突き抜ける！
No!
It's getting through!
ぬぁぁぁぁぁ‼
ゲフッ！
ウゲーッ‼
ぐおっ！
お… お…｡
I... I-I'm melting...
俺の体が溶けていく…｡
GUAHHHHH！
こ… この激痛！ この熱さ！
T-This pain... This heat!
WOOOOORRREEEEYYYYYY！
I was supposed to live on for centuries... For eternity...
何世紀も 未来へ…｡
永遠へ…
生きるはずの この ディオが！
I, the mighty Dio!
Begone, Dio...
散滅すべし ディオ！
I am the mighty Dio!
この ディオが！
なっ!?
うう！ 目から 自分の体液を！
He expelled the rest of his fluids from his eyes?!
あと 数cm 右にいたら
脳は破壊されていた！
If I had been hit just a few centimeters to the right...
my brain would have been pierced!
This is bad!
あ… 危ねえ！
断末魔！ この世に しがみつく
悪鬼の 最後のあがきよ！
It's his final act. One final act of defiance
before his evil vanishes from this world.
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)おお！
ディオが 崖下へ落ちていくぞ！
Dio's falling off the cliff!
おおおお～ッ‼
ディオ…｡
Dio...
(ポコ)あっ！ お兄ちゃんが！
Hey, mister!
He's just exhausted.
疲労だぜ！ 無理もねえ｡
Can't blame him either. He's fought countless
life or death battles in a single night.
たった 一晩に 何人も死んでいる
戦いをしてきたんだ！
But, why was he crying when he beat a bad guy?
(ポコ)でも 何だって 悪いやつを
やっつけたのに 涙を流してるの？
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)それは 彼の青春は
ディオとの青春でもあったからさ｡
It's because he spent his youth alongside Dio.
だがな 俺は 大いに笑うぜ！
Still, I can be happy in his place!
見てるかい ツェペリのおっさん！
Did you see that, old man Zeppeli?
He did it... Mr. Joestar finally did it!
やったぞ！➡
ジョースターさんが
ついに やった！➡
Dio is dead.
ディオは死んだ！➡
大げさかもしれんが
世界は 救われたんだ‼
I'm not one to exaggerate, but I daresay we saved the world!
♬(ｴﾝﾃﾞｨﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
I'll be the roundabout
♬ I'll be the roundabout
The words will make you out 'n' out
♬ The words
will make you out'n'out
♬ You spend the day away
We spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through the sound and
♬ Call it morning
driving through
♬ the sound and
in and out the valley
In and out the valley... hey!
♬ In and around the lake
In and around the lake
♬ Mountains come out of
the sky and they stand there
Mountains come out of the sky
and they stand there
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
♬ One mile over we'll be there
and we'll see you
♬ Ten true summers
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
♬ we'll be there
and laughing too
♬ Twenty four before
my love you'll see
Twenty four before my love you'll see I'll be
♬ I'll be there with you
there with you
♬～
Next Episode
It's a damn fine thing!
They're tears of joy.
R-Run...
As long as we're together, I wouldn't mind staying like this forever...
My body... I've found it.
Episode 9:
"The Final Ripple!"
(ｽﾋﾟｰﾄﾞﾜｺﾞﾝ)まったく めでたいぜ！
(ｴﾘﾅ)この涙は 幸せの涙です｡
に… 逃げるんだ｡
(ｴﾘﾅ)２人一緒なら
ずっと こうしていたい｡
ボディー… 来たか｡